<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>maskah &#8211; 2PP Over Tribler</title>
	<atom:link href="https://2pp.over.tribler.org/author/maskah/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://2pp.over.tribler.org</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 06:15:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://2pp.over.tribler.org/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/over.png</url>
	<title>maskah &#8211; 2PP Over Tribler</title>
	<link>https://2pp.over.tribler.org</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Travel to all countries is over, this time he made his own country</title>
		<link>https://2pp.over.tribler.org/travel-to-all-countries-is-over-this-time-he-made-his-own-country/</link>
					<comments>https://2pp.over.tribler.org/travel-to-all-countries-is-over-this-time-he-made-his-own-country/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[maskah]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 05:26:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Weird news]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://localhost/xoxlzkd/?p=37</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[American citizen Randy Williams has visited almost all the countries of the world that are members of the United Nations. With only one country left to travel, he fell into thinking, where will he go next! How to overcome his wanderlust. From this thought he started planning to create a new country. In the end, [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>American citizen Randy Williams has visited almost all the countries of the world that are members of the United Nations. With only one country left to travel, he fell into thinking, where will he go next! How to overcome his wanderlust. From this thought he started planning to create a new country. In the end, Williams, a professional radio broadcaster, bought 11.07 acres of empty land in the desert and declared it as a new country.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img decoding="async" width="630" height="415" src="http://localhost/xoxlzkd/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Sultan-Williams-of-Slojamastan-likes-to-take-pictures-with-people-wearing-bright-green-clothes.png" alt="" class="wp-image-41"/></figure>



<p>He named the country &#8216;Slojamastan&#8217; after his radio show. Dublandia named the capital of Slozamastan Republic. And the &#8216;Sultan&#8217; of Slojamastan is Williams himself.</p>



<p>On December 1, 2021, at 12:26 PM local time in the United States, Sultan Williams of Slojamastan officially declared the independence of Slojamastan. At that time he was wearing a suit and sunglasses. He broadcast the program live from the &#8216;Government Office&#8217; built under the open sky in the capital of the self-proclaimed country.</p>



<p>Two years after the official announcement, Sultan Williams introduced several bizarre laws in his country, including banning citizens from wearing sandals. This republic also has its own passport and flag. He launched his own currency called &#8216;Double&#8217;. Apart from this, he also introduced the practice of playing his own national anthem at state events.</p>



<p>Sultan Williams claims that there are more than five hundred registered citizens in the Republic of Slojamastan. Apart from this, another 4500 people have been granted conditional residence permit. They are waiting for citizenship. Williams calls this self-proclaimed country a &#8216;micronation&#8217;. He invites tourists to visit Slojamastan.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Sultan of Slojamastan</h2>



<p>Among the 193 countries declared by the United Nations, Williams did not only visit Turkmenistan. He said, &#8216;When I&#8217;m not on the radio show, I&#8217;m probably traveling to a country that most people haven&#8217;t heard of before. I want to travel to the 194th country after the 193 countries declared by the United Nations. This is basically why I made Slojamastan country.&#8217;</p>



<p>Williams&#8217; self-proclaimed homeland of Slojamastan is located off State Route 78 in California. It is a two and a half hour drive northwest of San Diego. Williams has put up a huge signboard on the side of the highway that says &#8216;Welcome to Slozamastan&#8217;. Apart from setting up a border control post, he hoisted the colorful flag of Slojamastan over his minister&#8217;s office.</p>



<p>Williams has seen such self-proclaimed &#8216;micronation&#8217; within different countries during his world travels. After seeing these things he was inspired to build a country himself.</p>



<p>In August 2021, Williams traveled to the 11.3-acre micronation Republic of Molossia in Nevada. In 1998, the republic declared independence from the United States. The country&#8217;s president, Kevin Bugg, showed him around the country. At that time, Williams&#8217; passport had to be stamped and photographed at the border. He learned of the Molossian Republic&#8217;s ongoing &#8216;war&#8217; with the now-defunct East Germany. The country also has a local currency called Valora.</p>



<p>Returning to San Diego after the trip, Williams quickly began planning his own micronation. In October 2021, he bought land for a country called Slozamastan with US$19,000 and declared the independence of the self-proclaimed country by December.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Dictatorship in the desert</h2>



<p>Williams said about the government system of Slozamastan, &#8216;Even though it is a republic, most of the time we run the country in a dictatorial manner. In the future we will organize special polls and referendums. Recently I have allowed citizens to vote on what should be the name of the country&#8217;s national fruit, game and animal.&#8217;<br>It may seem paradoxical to have an autocratic Sultan as the head of state in a republic, but this is the norm in this country. Williams has traveled to many strange places around the world. Saw the same rules in those places too. He also notes these dilemmas in countries like the People&#8217;s Republic of North Korea.</p>



<p>Williams likes to pose with people in a bright green sultan dress. He wears a green dress with his own military award, a gold badge attached to a military officer&#8217;s uniform, and light-colored sunglasses. This is basically his Sultan&#8217;s dress. Williams hires &#8216;border guards&#8217; for Slojamastan. Apart from this, he is always surrounded by security guards.</p>



<p>Slojamastan country also has a website. Apply for citizenship and cabinet posts on this website. This rule has become popular. Because, thousands of applications have already been submitted on the website.</p>



<p>Williams has opened the borders of Slojamastan to tourists. Popular tourist spots in the country right now include taking a selfie in front of the &#8216;Slojamastan&#8217; sign, visiting Independence Square and spotting the national animal, the raccoon.<br>Williams said plans to raise funds include a lazy river, an armadillo farm and a giant statue of the great leader (himself) at Slojamastan. He also said, &#8216;Throughout the year we conduct several activities. These include getting citizens&#8217; passports stamped in Slozamastan, attending commemorations of the formation of the new country and meeting the Sultan.&#8217;</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Seeking diplomatic recognition</h2>



<p>Sultan Williams of Slojamastan said that he is working to establish diplomatic relations with other countries. He has so far traveled to 16 countries including South Africa, New Zealand, Vanuatu and the United States with a Slojamastan passport.</p>



<p>Strategically, Slozamastan met all of the criteria set out in the 1933 Montevideo Convention for becoming a sovereign nation-state, Williams explained. The Montevideo Convention definition of country is by far the most accepted definition.</p>



<p>According to the Montevideo Convention, a country must have a permanent population, a fixed territory, a government and the ability to establish diplomatic relations with other states. Williams claimed that Slozamastan fulfilled these conditions.</p>



<p>Williams&#8217; next plan is to get Slozamastan recognized as a micronation by the United States. However, it will not be easy for him to get this recognition.</p>



<p>Sultan said, &#8216;I have sent e-mails and private messages to US President Joe Biden on Facebook, Twitter, Instagram and MySpace but have not received any response. All my messages are unread. I was a bit disappointed by this. Perhaps the messages are stuck in his spam folder. But we will try.&#8217;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://2pp.over.tribler.org/travel-to-all-countries-is-over-this-time-he-made-his-own-country/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>NPR’s Terence Samuel Is Named Top Editor of USA Today</title>
		<link>https://2pp.over.tribler.org/nprs-terence-samuel-is-named-top-editor-of-usa-today/</link>
					<comments>https://2pp.over.tribler.org/nprs-terence-samuel-is-named-top-editor-of-usa-today/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[maskah]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 17:43:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[NPR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Terence Samuel]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[USA]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://localhost/myclimate/?p=27</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Terence Samuel, a top news executive at National Public Radio, will be the next editor in chief of USA Today. Gannett, the nation’s largest newspaper chain and the publisher of USA Today, made the announcement on Friday. Mr. Samuel, who will start on July 10, fills a position vacated in May by Nicole Carroll, who had [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Terence Samuel, a top news executive at National Public Radio, will be the next editor in chief of USA Today.</p>



<p>Gannett, the nation’s largest newspaper chain and the publisher of USA Today, made the announcement on Friday. Mr. Samuel, who will start on July 10, fills a position vacated in May by Nicole Carroll, who had led USA Today for five years.</p>



<p>Mr. Samuel, 61, is a vice president and executive editor at NPR, where he oversees all news gathering at the network. Before joining NPR in 2017, he was a deputy national political editor at The Washington Post, and he has also worked at The Root, The Philadelphia Inquirer and U.S. News &amp; World Report.</p>



<p>Mr. Samuel said in a statement that he was honored to help lead USA Today, which made its debut in 1982, “into a digital future.”</p>



<p>“USA Today has a distinctive and groundbreaking history in American journalism and is uniquely positioned to inform the conversations and tell the stories that impact American life,” he said.</p>



<p>Kristin Roberts, Gannett’s chief content officer, said Mr. Samuel would “accelerate our transformation of USA Today, embracing our role and our roots as America’s newspaper with the core mission of being nothing less than essential to the readers, viewers and listeners we serve nationwide.”</p>



<p>In an email to NPR staff on Friday, Edith Chapin, the interim senior vice president for news, said the network would conduct a national search to find his replacement.</p>



<p>Mr. Samuel joins Gannett at a perilous time. The company, struggling under a debt burden from its 2019 merger with GateHouse Media, has had multiple rounds of layoffs in recent years. Its stock price has plummeted nearly 70 percent since the merger.</p>



<p>Hundreds of journalists from about two dozen Gannett newsrooms plan to walk off the job on Monday during the company’s annual shareholder meeting in protest over its executive leadership.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://2pp.over.tribler.org/nprs-terence-samuel-is-named-top-editor-of-usa-today/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Debt ceiling deal reveals the impotence of Donald Trump&#8217;s MAGA movement</title>
		<link>https://2pp.over.tribler.org/debt-ceiling-deal-reveals-the-impotence-of-donald-trumps-maga-movement/</link>
					<comments>https://2pp.over.tribler.org/debt-ceiling-deal-reveals-the-impotence-of-donald-trumps-maga-movement/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[maskah]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 17:39:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Donald Trump]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MAGA movement]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[McCarthy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://localhost/myclimate/?p=24</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[I have bad news for folks who invested in bright red “Make America Great Again” hats and devoted years of their lives to what former President Donald Trump routinely calls “the greatest political movement in the history of our country.” The MAGA movement, with each passing day, appears smaller and more impotent. It’s loud but ineffective, capable [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>I have bad news for folks who invested in bright red “Make America Great Again” hats and devoted years of their lives to what former President Donald Trump routinely calls “the greatest political movement in the history of our country.”</p>



<p>The MAGA movement, with each passing day, appears smaller and more impotent. It’s loud but ineffective, capable of creating chaos but incapable of success.</p>



<p>The recent debt ceiling deal reached between President Joe Biden and Republican House Speaker Kevin McCarthy perfectly illustrates MAGA’s all-holler/no-action status.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">MAGA&#8217;s debt ceiling red line was easily crossed by Kevin McCarthy</h2>



<p>This was the none-shall-pass moment for far-right Republicans in Congress, a chance to use the threat of economic disaster that would accompany a default to undo all the things Big Bad Biden has accomplished as president, to slash spending to the bone and poke holes in the safety net.</p>



<p>“I say to the Republicans out there – congressmen, senators – if they don’t give you massive cuts, you’re going to have to do a default,&#8221; Trump said during a CNN town hall.</p>



<p>Republican Rep. Kevin Hern of Oklahoma, chair of the Republican Study Committee told Axios that he agreed with Trump. And Rep. Ralph Norman of South Carolina said: “Either they agree to cuts, which are modest, or they take responsibility for whatever happens.”</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">The Republican Party&#8217;s debt ceiling threats met up with reality</h2>



<p>McCarthy caved to MAGA demands and initially produced a debt ceiling bill that would have gutted much of what Biden accomplished in his first two years. It was a wholly unreasonable proposal, aimed at appeasing the extremes of McCarthy&#8217;s own party.</p>



<p>But the final deal the speaker hammered out with Biden was nothing close to what MAGA lawmakers wanted.</p>



<p><strong>Trump unleashes DeSantis deepfake:</strong>GOP should support a grownup for president.</p>



<p><strong>Game on.</strong>With DeSantis making it official on Twitter, the fight against Trump can begin.</p>



<p>The original bill sought a 10-year cap on spending, with draconian cuts to non-Defense spending. The final deal puts minor spending restraints in place for the next two years. They wanted strict (and unnecessary) work requirements on food stamps recipients and people on Medicaid. Medicaid went untouched, and the dynamics of the change in work requirements for Supplemental Nutrition Assistance Program recipients, according to the nonpartisan Congressional Budget Office, will actually increase government spending on food stamps.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://2pp.over.tribler.org/debt-ceiling-deal-reveals-the-impotence-of-donald-trumps-maga-movement/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Saudi Arabia is reducing oil production, there is a fear of price increase</title>
		<link>https://2pp.over.tribler.org/saudi-arabia-is-reducing-oil-production-there-is-a-fear-of-price-increase/</link>
					<comments>https://2pp.over.tribler.org/saudi-arabia-is-reducing-oil-production-there-is-a-fear-of-price-increase/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[maskah]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 16:02:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Saudi Arabia]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[the market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[the oil]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://localhost/ntt-com/?p=17</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Saudi Arabia has announced to reduce oil production by another 1 million barrels per day. It is believed that such a decision has been taken to increase the price of oil in the world market by reducing the supply. The announcement was made after a meeting between the 13-nation Organization of the Petroleum Exporting Countries [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Saudi Arabia has announced to reduce oil production by another 1 million barrels per day. It is believed that such a decision has been taken to increase the price of oil in the world market by reducing the supply.</p>



<p>The announcement was made after a meeting between the 13-nation Organization of the Petroleum Exporting Countries (OPEC) and its 10 allies led by Saudi Arabia. Russia led the Allies. OPEC and 10 allied countries are called OPEC Plus.</p>



<p>Saudi Arabia&#8217;s Energy Minister Prince Abdulaziz bin Salman told reporters that the decision to cut production was made for the month of July. Its duration may be extended.</p>



<p>The decision to cut &#8216;voluntary&#8217; production was announced after representatives of OPEC plus countries took part in several hours of talks in the Austrian capital Vienna.</p>



<p>A source involved in this discussion says that there has been a discussion about reducing production by 1 million barrels per day.</p>



<p>About 60 percent of the world&#8217;s total oil is produced in OPEC plus countries. Oil-producing nations have struggled to cope with falling oil prices and volatile markets since Russia&#8217;s invasion of Ukraine began in February 2022.</p>



<p>Last April, several OPEC Plus members agreed to voluntarily cut production by more than 1 million barrels a day. Although this sudden action reduced the price of oil, it was not sustainable for long.<br>Oil prices fell nearly 10 percent after announcing production cuts in April. Brent crude oil prices fell to $70 per barrel. This is the first time since December 2021 that the price of Brent crude has fallen so much.</p>



<p>Russian Deputy Prime Minister Alexander Novak said that the current decision to cut production may be extended until the end of 2024 after testing.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://2pp.over.tribler.org/saudi-arabia-is-reducing-oil-production-there-is-a-fear-of-price-increase/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Record of foreigners taking citizenship in Germany</title>
		<link>https://2pp.over.tribler.org/record-of-foreigners-taking-citizenship-in-germany/</link>
					<comments>https://2pp.over.tribler.org/record-of-foreigners-taking-citizenship-in-germany/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[maskah]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 16:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Germany]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://localhost/ntt-com/?p=14</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A record number of foreigners took up citizenship in Germany last year. This number is the highest in the last 20 years. According to the government&#8217;s calculations, in 2022, 168,545 people from 171 countries of the world took German citizenship. This number is 28 percent more than the previous year, i.e. 2021. Syrians top the [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>A record number of foreigners took up citizenship in Germany last year. This number is the highest in the last 20 years.</p>



<p>According to the government&#8217;s calculations, in 2022, 168,545 people from 171 countries of the world took German citizenship. This number is 28 percent more than the previous year, i.e. 2021.</p>



<p>Syrians top the list of foreigners granted citizenship. The average age of people who have taken German citizenship from the war-torn Middle Eastern country is 25 years (24.8). Two-thirds of them are men. They stayed in the country for an average of six and a half years (6.4) before getting citizenship.</p>



<p>Ukrainians are second in the list of German citizens. Thousands of Ukrainians fled the country after the Russian offensive began. A part of them took refuge in Germany.</p>



<p>In 2022, immigrants from Iraq, another war-torn country in the Middle East, ranked third among immigrants who received German citizenship. And the Turks are in the fourth position.</p>



<p>Ian Schneider, an expert at the Department of Integration and Migration, said that half of the Syrians who got citizenship got German citizenship within six years. The reason for this is that they have been able to show evidence of integration into German society.</p>



<p>According to Schleider, the German citizenship of Syrians will increase this year. Because, the current coalition government in power is working to simplify the citizenship law.</p>



<p>Currently, in order to obtain German citizenship, a candidate must demonstrate eight years of residence in Germany and proof of German language proficiency (B1 level). Along with passing a special written test for citizenship. Apart from this, there is a requirement to have the financial ability to operate without state aid and to have no criminal record.</p>



<p>However, due to the shortage of skilled workers in the country, the ruling coalition government led by Olaf Schultz is trying to amend the citizenship law. The government believes that easing citizenship laws will encourage skilled foreign workers to immigrate to the country.</p>



<p>Interior Minister Nancy Fesser&#8217;s proposed new citizenship law calls for three major changes.</p>



<p>Under the proposed new law, citizenship can be applied for after five years of legal residence in Germany instead of eight. Apart from this, there is an opportunity to apply after three years of residence if you can show proof of integration in the society.</p>



<p>If one of the parents of a child born in Germany has lived legally in the country for five years, the child is eligible for German citizenship.</p>



<p>Apart from this, it is said that the facility of holding dual citizenship is also being kept in the new law.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://2pp.over.tribler.org/record-of-foreigners-taking-citizenship-in-germany/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Austin-Rajnath discussed military alliance</title>
		<link>https://2pp.over.tribler.org/austin-rajnath-discussed-military-alliance/</link>
					<comments>https://2pp.over.tribler.org/austin-rajnath-discussed-military-alliance/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[maskah]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 15:57:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[defense]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[India]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://localhost/ntt-com/?p=10</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[India and the US have jointly decided on a direction to move forward in expanding areas of cooperation in defense manufacturing and technology transfer. US Defense Minister Austin Lloyd&#8217;s two-day visit to India held a detailed discussion on this issue on Monday. After talks with India&#8217;s Defense Minister Rajnath Singh, US Defense Secretary Lloyd Austin [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>India and the US have jointly decided on a direction to move forward in expanding areas of cooperation in defense manufacturing and technology transfer. US Defense Minister Austin Lloyd&#8217;s two-day visit to India held a detailed discussion on this issue on Monday.</p>



<p>After talks with India&#8217;s Defense Minister Rajnath Singh, US Defense Secretary Lloyd Austin told media representatives, &#8216;The relationship between the two countries is improving rapidly. We are now looking at expanding the scope of defense industry cooperation.&#8217;</p>



<p>The main objective of this cooperation in defense manufacturing is to make India &#8216;self-reliant&#8217; and implement the &#8216;Make in India&#8217; slogan. After the &#8216;warm and sincere&#8217; meeting of the two defense ministers, the statement of the Ministry of Defense of India said that policy guidelines have been prepared for how the two countries will expand the area of ​​mutual cooperation in the next few years. Accordingly, the two countries will identify new technology-based defense production areas. Emphasis will also be placed on technology transfer to scale up production.</p>



<p>The two leaders also discussed enhancing defense ties. After the meeting, Indian Defense Minister Rajnath Singh said that it is important to keep India and the Pacific region under free, unfettered and legal governance and deepen the relationship between the two countries to ensure that. For that, India is ready to work more closely with the US to build strategic ties and enhance defense capabilities.</p>



<p>Before the visit, it was reported by informed sources that General Electric of the United States is interested in transferring the technology of manufacturing fighter aircraft engines to India. Apart from this, India has also shown interest in buying 30 &#8216;MQ-9B&#8217; armed drones from the US for $3 billion. These issues will be considered during the visit to Austin. However, after the meeting of the two ministers, nothing specific was said about it. However, it is believed that the US Defense Secretary&#8217;s visit is very indicative ahead of Indian Prime Minister Narendra Modi&#8217;s upcoming US visit.<br>Russia supplies the bulk of India&#8217;s defense equipment and armaments. Despite that long-standing relationship, India has also started buying military weapons from the US, France and Israel over the years.</p>



<p>Before coming to India, Austin attended the &#8216;Sangri La Dialogue&#8217;, a security summit in Singapore. China&#8217;s Defense Minister Li Shangfu warned that the formation of a military alliance like &#8220;NATO&#8221; in the Asia-Pacific region will plunge the entire region into a whirlwind of conflict. The United States has taken steps to create a NATO-like military alliance in the region to counter China&#8217;s speculation. They are keen to include India in that alliance.</p>



<p>While Rajnath Singh&#8217;s meeting with Austin discussed keeping the Indo-Pacific region &#8216;fear-free and free&#8217;, there was no word from any quarter on whether the proposal to form a military alliance like NATO was discussed or not. Lloyd Austin also held a meeting with India&#8217;s National Security Advisor Ajit Doval today.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://2pp.over.tribler.org/austin-rajnath-discussed-military-alliance/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The president of Barca took away the journalist&#8217;s phone for questioning Messi&#8217;s return</title>
		<link>https://2pp.over.tribler.org/the-president-of-barca-took-away-the-journalists-phone-for-questioning-messis-return/</link>
					<comments>https://2pp.over.tribler.org/the-president-of-barca-took-away-the-journalists-phone-for-questioning-messis-return/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[maskah]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 15:54:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Barcelona]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[messi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PSG]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://localhost/ntt-com/?p=7</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[One question the football world has already answered is whether Lionel Messi&#8217;s two-year relationship with PSG has ended. There is also a question about Messi, which is now a question of billions of dollars in the football world &#8211; where will Messi go? Al Hilal officials are currently in Paris, according to news agency AFP. [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>One question the football world has already answered is whether Lionel Messi&#8217;s two-year relationship with PSG has ended. There is also a question about Messi, which is now a question of billions of dollars in the football world &#8211; where will Messi go?</p>



<p>Al Hilal officials are currently in Paris, according to news agency AFP. They went there to talk to Messi&#8217;s father and agent Jorge Messi to finalize the deal. AFP wrote in their news that the official announcement of the finalization of the contract will be made by the Saudi Arabian club before the beginning of the week.</p>



<p>Even with such news, there is no shortage of expectations about Messi&#8217;s return to Barcelona. The club&#8217;s supporters at Camp Nou are still hoping that Messi will return. Messi signed from Barcelona to PSG in 2021. While AFP is reporting on the final stage of the contract with Al Hilal on the Argentine World Cup-winning star, journalists close to Barcelona are asking the president of the club, Juan Laporta, what is the probability of Messi&#8217;s return?</p>



<p>Laporta was asked this question yesterday by a journalist who turned on his cell phone recorder to record what Laporta said. Then Laporta showed a strange reaction.</p>



<p>According to Argentinian media TYC, Laporta grabbed the journalist&#8217;s phone and put it in his pocket. Then he said, &#8216;You will see if it is difficult to return Messi.&#8217; After a while, however, Laporta returned the journalist&#8217;s mobile phone.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://2pp.over.tribler.org/the-president-of-barca-took-away-the-journalists-phone-for-questioning-messis-return/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
