<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>the oil &#8211; Staging Skyway ntt</title>
	<atom:link href="https://staging.skyway.ntt.com/tag/the-oil/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://staging.skyway.ntt.com</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 16:02:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Saudi Arabia is reducing oil production, there is a fear of price increase</title>
		<link>https://staging.skyway.ntt.com/saudi-arabia-is-reducing-oil-production-there-is-a-fear-of-price-increase/</link>
					<comments>https://staging.skyway.ntt.com/saudi-arabia-is-reducing-oil-production-there-is-a-fear-of-price-increase/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[alaminae]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 16:02:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Saudi Arabia]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[the market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[the oil]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://staging.skyway.ntt.com/?p=17</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Saudi Arabia has announced to reduce oil production by another 1 million barrels per day. It is believed that such a decision has been taken to increase the price of oil in the world market by reducing the supply. The announcement was made after a meeting between the 13-nation Organization of the Petroleum Exporting Countries [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Saudi Arabia has announced to reduce oil production by another 1 million barrels per day. It is believed that such a decision has been taken to increase the price of oil in the world market by reducing the supply.</p>



<p>The announcement was made after a meeting between the 13-nation Organization of the Petroleum Exporting Countries (OPEC) and its 10 allies led by Saudi Arabia. Russia led the Allies. OPEC and 10 allied countries are called OPEC Plus.</p>



<p>Saudi Arabia&#8217;s Energy Minister Prince Abdulaziz bin Salman told reporters that the decision to cut production was made for the month of July. Its duration may be extended.</p>



<p>The decision to cut &#8216;voluntary&#8217; production was announced after representatives of OPEC plus countries took part in several hours of talks in the Austrian capital Vienna.</p>



<p>A source involved in this discussion says that there has been a discussion about reducing production by 1 million barrels per day.</p>



<p>About 60 percent of the world&#8217;s total oil is produced in OPEC plus countries. Oil-producing nations have struggled to cope with falling oil prices and volatile markets since Russia&#8217;s invasion of Ukraine began in February 2022.</p>



<p>Last April, several OPEC Plus members agreed to voluntarily cut production by more than 1 million barrels a day. Although this sudden action reduced the price of oil, it was not sustainable for long.<br>Oil prices fell nearly 10 percent after announcing production cuts in April. Brent crude oil prices fell to $70 per barrel. This is the first time since December 2021 that the price of Brent crude has fallen so much.</p>



<p>Russian Deputy Prime Minister Alexander Novak said that the current decision to cut production may be extended until the end of 2024 after testing.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://staging.skyway.ntt.com/saudi-arabia-is-reducing-oil-production-there-is-a-fear-of-price-increase/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
