<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MAGA movement &#8211; 2PP Over Tribler</title>
	<atom:link href="https://2pp.over.tribler.org/tag/maga-movement/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://2pp.over.tribler.org</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 17:39:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://2pp.over.tribler.org/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/over.png</url>
	<title>MAGA movement &#8211; 2PP Over Tribler</title>
	<link>https://2pp.over.tribler.org</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Debt ceiling deal reveals the impotence of Donald Trump&#8217;s MAGA movement</title>
		<link>https://2pp.over.tribler.org/debt-ceiling-deal-reveals-the-impotence-of-donald-trumps-maga-movement/</link>
					<comments>https://2pp.over.tribler.org/debt-ceiling-deal-reveals-the-impotence-of-donald-trumps-maga-movement/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[maskah]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 17:39:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Donald Trump]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[MAGA movement]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[McCarthy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://localhost/myclimate/?p=24</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[I have bad news for folks who invested in bright red “Make America Great Again” hats and devoted years of their lives to what former President Donald Trump routinely calls “the greatest political movement in the history of our country.” The MAGA movement, with each passing day, appears smaller and more impotent. It’s loud but ineffective, capable [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>I have bad news for folks who invested in bright red “Make America Great Again” hats and devoted years of their lives to what former President Donald Trump routinely calls “the greatest political movement in the history of our country.”</p>



<p>The MAGA movement, with each passing day, appears smaller and more impotent. It’s loud but ineffective, capable of creating chaos but incapable of success.</p>



<p>The recent debt ceiling deal reached between President Joe Biden and Republican House Speaker Kevin McCarthy perfectly illustrates MAGA’s all-holler/no-action status.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">MAGA&#8217;s debt ceiling red line was easily crossed by Kevin McCarthy</h2>



<p>This was the none-shall-pass moment for far-right Republicans in Congress, a chance to use the threat of economic disaster that would accompany a default to undo all the things Big Bad Biden has accomplished as president, to slash spending to the bone and poke holes in the safety net.</p>



<p>“I say to the Republicans out there – congressmen, senators – if they don’t give you massive cuts, you’re going to have to do a default,&#8221; Trump said during a CNN town hall.</p>



<p>Republican Rep. Kevin Hern of Oklahoma, chair of the Republican Study Committee told Axios that he agreed with Trump. And Rep. Ralph Norman of South Carolina said: “Either they agree to cuts, which are modest, or they take responsibility for whatever happens.”</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">The Republican Party&#8217;s debt ceiling threats met up with reality</h2>



<p>McCarthy caved to MAGA demands and initially produced a debt ceiling bill that would have gutted much of what Biden accomplished in his first two years. It was a wholly unreasonable proposal, aimed at appeasing the extremes of McCarthy&#8217;s own party.</p>



<p>But the final deal the speaker hammered out with Biden was nothing close to what MAGA lawmakers wanted.</p>



<p><strong>Trump unleashes DeSantis deepfake:</strong>GOP should support a grownup for president.</p>



<p><strong>Game on.</strong>With DeSantis making it official on Twitter, the fight against Trump can begin.</p>



<p>The original bill sought a 10-year cap on spending, with draconian cuts to non-Defense spending. The final deal puts minor spending restraints in place for the next two years. They wanted strict (and unnecessary) work requirements on food stamps recipients and people on Medicaid. Medicaid went untouched, and the dynamics of the change in work requirements for Supplemental Nutrition Assistance Program recipients, according to the nonpartisan Congressional Budget Office, will actually increase government spending on food stamps.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://2pp.over.tribler.org/debt-ceiling-deal-reveals-the-impotence-of-donald-trumps-maga-movement/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
