<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Staging Skyway ntt</title>
	<atom:link href="https://staging.skyway.ntt.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://staging.skyway.ntt.com</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 16:02:48 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Saudi Arabia is reducing oil production, there is a fear of price increase</title>
		<link>https://staging.skyway.ntt.com/saudi-arabia-is-reducing-oil-production-there-is-a-fear-of-price-increase/</link>
					<comments>https://staging.skyway.ntt.com/saudi-arabia-is-reducing-oil-production-there-is-a-fear-of-price-increase/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[alaminae]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 16:02:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Saudi Arabia]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[the market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[the oil]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://staging.skyway.ntt.com/?p=17</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Saudi Arabia has announced to reduce oil production by another 1 million barrels per day. It is believed that such a decision has been taken to increase the price of oil in the world market by reducing the supply. The announcement was made after a meeting between the 13-nation Organization of the Petroleum Exporting Countries [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Saudi Arabia has announced to reduce oil production by another 1 million barrels per day. It is believed that such a decision has been taken to increase the price of oil in the world market by reducing the supply.</p>



<p>The announcement was made after a meeting between the 13-nation Organization of the Petroleum Exporting Countries (OPEC) and its 10 allies led by Saudi Arabia. Russia led the Allies. OPEC and 10 allied countries are called OPEC Plus.</p>



<p>Saudi Arabia&#8217;s Energy Minister Prince Abdulaziz bin Salman told reporters that the decision to cut production was made for the month of July. Its duration may be extended.</p>



<p>The decision to cut &#8216;voluntary&#8217; production was announced after representatives of OPEC plus countries took part in several hours of talks in the Austrian capital Vienna.</p>



<p>A source involved in this discussion says that there has been a discussion about reducing production by 1 million barrels per day.</p>



<p>About 60 percent of the world&#8217;s total oil is produced in OPEC plus countries. Oil-producing nations have struggled to cope with falling oil prices and volatile markets since Russia&#8217;s invasion of Ukraine began in February 2022.</p>



<p>Last April, several OPEC Plus members agreed to voluntarily cut production by more than 1 million barrels a day. Although this sudden action reduced the price of oil, it was not sustainable for long.<br>Oil prices fell nearly 10 percent after announcing production cuts in April. Brent crude oil prices fell to $70 per barrel. This is the first time since December 2021 that the price of Brent crude has fallen so much.</p>



<p>Russian Deputy Prime Minister Alexander Novak said that the current decision to cut production may be extended until the end of 2024 after testing.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://staging.skyway.ntt.com/saudi-arabia-is-reducing-oil-production-there-is-a-fear-of-price-increase/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Record of foreigners taking citizenship in Germany</title>
		<link>https://staging.skyway.ntt.com/record-of-foreigners-taking-citizenship-in-germany/</link>
					<comments>https://staging.skyway.ntt.com/record-of-foreigners-taking-citizenship-in-germany/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[alaminae]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 16:00:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Germany]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://staging.skyway.ntt.com/?p=14</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A record number of foreigners took up citizenship in Germany last year. This number is the highest in the last 20 years. According to the government&#8217;s calculations, in 2022, 168,545 people from 171 countries of the world took German citizenship. This number is 28 percent more than the previous year, i.e. 2021. Syrians top the [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>A record number of foreigners took up citizenship in Germany last year. This number is the highest in the last 20 years.</p>



<p>According to the government&#8217;s calculations, in 2022, 168,545 people from 171 countries of the world took German citizenship. This number is 28 percent more than the previous year, i.e. 2021.</p>



<p>Syrians top the list of foreigners granted citizenship. The average age of people who have taken German citizenship from the war-torn Middle Eastern country is 25 years (24.8). Two-thirds of them are men. They stayed in the country for an average of six and a half years (6.4) before getting citizenship.</p>



<p>Ukrainians are second in the list of German citizens. Thousands of Ukrainians fled the country after the Russian offensive began. A part of them took refuge in Germany.</p>



<p>In 2022, immigrants from Iraq, another war-torn country in the Middle East, ranked third among immigrants who received German citizenship. And the Turks are in the fourth position.</p>



<p>Ian Schneider, an expert at the Department of Integration and Migration, said that half of the Syrians who got citizenship got German citizenship within six years. The reason for this is that they have been able to show evidence of integration into German society.</p>



<p>According to Schleider, the German citizenship of Syrians will increase this year. Because, the current coalition government in power is working to simplify the citizenship law.</p>



<p>Currently, in order to obtain German citizenship, a candidate must demonstrate eight years of residence in Germany and proof of German language proficiency (B1 level). Along with passing a special written test for citizenship. Apart from this, there is a requirement to have the financial ability to operate without state aid and to have no criminal record.</p>



<p>However, due to the shortage of skilled workers in the country, the ruling coalition government led by Olaf Schultz is trying to amend the citizenship law. The government believes that easing citizenship laws will encourage skilled foreign workers to immigrate to the country.</p>



<p>Interior Minister Nancy Fesser&#8217;s proposed new citizenship law calls for three major changes.</p>



<p>Under the proposed new law, citizenship can be applied for after five years of legal residence in Germany instead of eight. Apart from this, there is an opportunity to apply after three years of residence if you can show proof of integration in the society.</p>



<p>If one of the parents of a child born in Germany has lived legally in the country for five years, the child is eligible for German citizenship.</p>



<p>Apart from this, it is said that the facility of holding dual citizenship is also being kept in the new law.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://staging.skyway.ntt.com/record-of-foreigners-taking-citizenship-in-germany/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Austin-Rajnath discussed military alliance</title>
		<link>https://staging.skyway.ntt.com/austin-rajnath-discussed-military-alliance/</link>
					<comments>https://staging.skyway.ntt.com/austin-rajnath-discussed-military-alliance/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[alaminae]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 15:57:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[defense]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[India]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://staging.skyway.ntt.com/?p=10</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[India and the US have jointly decided on a direction to move forward in expanding areas of cooperation in defense manufacturing and technology transfer. US Defense Minister Austin Lloyd&#8217;s two-day visit to India held a detailed discussion on this issue on Monday. After talks with India&#8217;s Defense Minister Rajnath Singh, US Defense Secretary Lloyd Austin [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>India and the US have jointly decided on a direction to move forward in expanding areas of cooperation in defense manufacturing and technology transfer. US Defense Minister Austin Lloyd&#8217;s two-day visit to India held a detailed discussion on this issue on Monday.</p>



<p>After talks with India&#8217;s Defense Minister Rajnath Singh, US Defense Secretary Lloyd Austin told media representatives, &#8216;The relationship between the two countries is improving rapidly. We are now looking at expanding the scope of defense industry cooperation.&#8217;</p>



<p>The main objective of this cooperation in defense manufacturing is to make India &#8216;self-reliant&#8217; and implement the &#8216;Make in India&#8217; slogan. After the &#8216;warm and sincere&#8217; meeting of the two defense ministers, the statement of the Ministry of Defense of India said that policy guidelines have been prepared for how the two countries will expand the area of ​​mutual cooperation in the next few years. Accordingly, the two countries will identify new technology-based defense production areas. Emphasis will also be placed on technology transfer to scale up production.</p>



<p>The two leaders also discussed enhancing defense ties. After the meeting, Indian Defense Minister Rajnath Singh said that it is important to keep India and the Pacific region under free, unfettered and legal governance and deepen the relationship between the two countries to ensure that. For that, India is ready to work more closely with the US to build strategic ties and enhance defense capabilities.</p>



<p>Before the visit, it was reported by informed sources that General Electric of the United States is interested in transferring the technology of manufacturing fighter aircraft engines to India. Apart from this, India has also shown interest in buying 30 &#8216;MQ-9B&#8217; armed drones from the US for $3 billion. These issues will be considered during the visit to Austin. However, after the meeting of the two ministers, nothing specific was said about it. However, it is believed that the US Defense Secretary&#8217;s visit is very indicative ahead of Indian Prime Minister Narendra Modi&#8217;s upcoming US visit.<br>Russia supplies the bulk of India&#8217;s defense equipment and armaments. Despite that long-standing relationship, India has also started buying military weapons from the US, France and Israel over the years.</p>



<p>Before coming to India, Austin attended the &#8216;Sangri La Dialogue&#8217;, a security summit in Singapore. China&#8217;s Defense Minister Li Shangfu warned that the formation of a military alliance like &#8220;NATO&#8221; in the Asia-Pacific region will plunge the entire region into a whirlwind of conflict. The United States has taken steps to create a NATO-like military alliance in the region to counter China&#8217;s speculation. They are keen to include India in that alliance.</p>



<p>While Rajnath Singh&#8217;s meeting with Austin discussed keeping the Indo-Pacific region &#8216;fear-free and free&#8217;, there was no word from any quarter on whether the proposal to form a military alliance like NATO was discussed or not. Lloyd Austin also held a meeting with India&#8217;s National Security Advisor Ajit Doval today.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://staging.skyway.ntt.com/austin-rajnath-discussed-military-alliance/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The president of Barca took away the journalist&#8217;s phone for questioning Messi&#8217;s return</title>
		<link>https://staging.skyway.ntt.com/the-president-of-barca-took-away-the-journalists-phone-for-questioning-messis-return/</link>
					<comments>https://staging.skyway.ntt.com/the-president-of-barca-took-away-the-journalists-phone-for-questioning-messis-return/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[alaminae]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 15:54:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Barcelona]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[messi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[PSG]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://staging.skyway.ntt.com/?p=7</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[One question the football world has already answered is whether Lionel Messi&#8217;s two-year relationship with PSG has ended. There is also a question about Messi, which is now a question of billions of dollars in the football world &#8211; where will Messi go? Al Hilal officials are currently in Paris, according to news agency AFP. [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>One question the football world has already answered is whether Lionel Messi&#8217;s two-year relationship with PSG has ended. There is also a question about Messi, which is now a question of billions of dollars in the football world &#8211; where will Messi go?</p>



<p>Al Hilal officials are currently in Paris, according to news agency AFP. They went there to talk to Messi&#8217;s father and agent Jorge Messi to finalize the deal. AFP wrote in their news that the official announcement of the finalization of the contract will be made by the Saudi Arabian club before the beginning of the week.</p>



<p>Even with such news, there is no shortage of expectations about Messi&#8217;s return to Barcelona. The club&#8217;s supporters at Camp Nou are still hoping that Messi will return. Messi signed from Barcelona to PSG in 2021. While AFP is reporting on the final stage of the contract with Al Hilal on the Argentine World Cup-winning star, journalists close to Barcelona are asking the president of the club, Juan Laporta, what is the probability of Messi&#8217;s return?</p>



<p>Laporta was asked this question yesterday by a journalist who turned on his cell phone recorder to record what Laporta said. Then Laporta showed a strange reaction.</p>



<p>According to Argentinian media TYC, Laporta grabbed the journalist&#8217;s phone and put it in his pocket. Then he said, &#8216;You will see if it is difficult to return Messi.&#8217; After a while, however, Laporta returned the journalist&#8217;s mobile phone.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://staging.skyway.ntt.com/the-president-of-barca-took-away-the-journalists-phone-for-questioning-messis-return/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
