<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Weird news &#8211; 2PP Over Tribler</title>
	<atom:link href="https://2pp.over.tribler.org/tag/weird-news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://2pp.over.tribler.org</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 06:15:41 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://2pp.over.tribler.org/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/over.png</url>
	<title>Weird news &#8211; 2PP Over Tribler</title>
	<link>https://2pp.over.tribler.org</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Travel to all countries is over, this time he made his own country</title>
		<link>https://2pp.over.tribler.org/travel-to-all-countries-is-over-this-time-he-made-his-own-country/</link>
					<comments>https://2pp.over.tribler.org/travel-to-all-countries-is-over-this-time-he-made-his-own-country/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[maskah]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 05:26:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[United States]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Weird news]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://localhost/xoxlzkd/?p=37</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[American citizen Randy Williams has visited almost all the countries of the world that are members of the United Nations. With only one country left to travel, he fell into thinking, where will he go next! How to overcome his wanderlust. From this thought he started planning to create a new country. In the end, [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>American citizen Randy Williams has visited almost all the countries of the world that are members of the United Nations. With only one country left to travel, he fell into thinking, where will he go next! How to overcome his wanderlust. From this thought he started planning to create a new country. In the end, Williams, a professional radio broadcaster, bought 11.07 acres of empty land in the desert and declared it as a new country.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img decoding="async" width="630" height="415" src="http://localhost/xoxlzkd/wp-content/uploads/2023/06/Sultan-Williams-of-Slojamastan-likes-to-take-pictures-with-people-wearing-bright-green-clothes.png" alt="" class="wp-image-41"/></figure>



<p>He named the country &#8216;Slojamastan&#8217; after his radio show. Dublandia named the capital of Slozamastan Republic. And the &#8216;Sultan&#8217; of Slojamastan is Williams himself.</p>



<p>On December 1, 2021, at 12:26 PM local time in the United States, Sultan Williams of Slojamastan officially declared the independence of Slojamastan. At that time he was wearing a suit and sunglasses. He broadcast the program live from the &#8216;Government Office&#8217; built under the open sky in the capital of the self-proclaimed country.</p>



<p>Two years after the official announcement, Sultan Williams introduced several bizarre laws in his country, including banning citizens from wearing sandals. This republic also has its own passport and flag. He launched his own currency called &#8216;Double&#8217;. Apart from this, he also introduced the practice of playing his own national anthem at state events.</p>



<p>Sultan Williams claims that there are more than five hundred registered citizens in the Republic of Slojamastan. Apart from this, another 4500 people have been granted conditional residence permit. They are waiting for citizenship. Williams calls this self-proclaimed country a &#8216;micronation&#8217;. He invites tourists to visit Slojamastan.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Sultan of Slojamastan</h2>



<p>Among the 193 countries declared by the United Nations, Williams did not only visit Turkmenistan. He said, &#8216;When I&#8217;m not on the radio show, I&#8217;m probably traveling to a country that most people haven&#8217;t heard of before. I want to travel to the 194th country after the 193 countries declared by the United Nations. This is basically why I made Slojamastan country.&#8217;</p>



<p>Williams&#8217; self-proclaimed homeland of Slojamastan is located off State Route 78 in California. It is a two and a half hour drive northwest of San Diego. Williams has put up a huge signboard on the side of the highway that says &#8216;Welcome to Slozamastan&#8217;. Apart from setting up a border control post, he hoisted the colorful flag of Slojamastan over his minister&#8217;s office.</p>



<p>Williams has seen such self-proclaimed &#8216;micronation&#8217; within different countries during his world travels. After seeing these things he was inspired to build a country himself.</p>



<p>In August 2021, Williams traveled to the 11.3-acre micronation Republic of Molossia in Nevada. In 1998, the republic declared independence from the United States. The country&#8217;s president, Kevin Bugg, showed him around the country. At that time, Williams&#8217; passport had to be stamped and photographed at the border. He learned of the Molossian Republic&#8217;s ongoing &#8216;war&#8217; with the now-defunct East Germany. The country also has a local currency called Valora.</p>



<p>Returning to San Diego after the trip, Williams quickly began planning his own micronation. In October 2021, he bought land for a country called Slozamastan with US$19,000 and declared the independence of the self-proclaimed country by December.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Dictatorship in the desert</h2>



<p>Williams said about the government system of Slozamastan, &#8216;Even though it is a republic, most of the time we run the country in a dictatorial manner. In the future we will organize special polls and referendums. Recently I have allowed citizens to vote on what should be the name of the country&#8217;s national fruit, game and animal.&#8217;<br>It may seem paradoxical to have an autocratic Sultan as the head of state in a republic, but this is the norm in this country. Williams has traveled to many strange places around the world. Saw the same rules in those places too. He also notes these dilemmas in countries like the People&#8217;s Republic of North Korea.</p>



<p>Williams likes to pose with people in a bright green sultan dress. He wears a green dress with his own military award, a gold badge attached to a military officer&#8217;s uniform, and light-colored sunglasses. This is basically his Sultan&#8217;s dress. Williams hires &#8216;border guards&#8217; for Slojamastan. Apart from this, he is always surrounded by security guards.</p>



<p>Slojamastan country also has a website. Apply for citizenship and cabinet posts on this website. This rule has become popular. Because, thousands of applications have already been submitted on the website.</p>



<p>Williams has opened the borders of Slojamastan to tourists. Popular tourist spots in the country right now include taking a selfie in front of the &#8216;Slojamastan&#8217; sign, visiting Independence Square and spotting the national animal, the raccoon.<br>Williams said plans to raise funds include a lazy river, an armadillo farm and a giant statue of the great leader (himself) at Slojamastan. He also said, &#8216;Throughout the year we conduct several activities. These include getting citizens&#8217; passports stamped in Slozamastan, attending commemorations of the formation of the new country and meeting the Sultan.&#8217;</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">Seeking diplomatic recognition</h2>



<p>Sultan Williams of Slojamastan said that he is working to establish diplomatic relations with other countries. He has so far traveled to 16 countries including South Africa, New Zealand, Vanuatu and the United States with a Slojamastan passport.</p>



<p>Strategically, Slozamastan met all of the criteria set out in the 1933 Montevideo Convention for becoming a sovereign nation-state, Williams explained. The Montevideo Convention definition of country is by far the most accepted definition.</p>



<p>According to the Montevideo Convention, a country must have a permanent population, a fixed territory, a government and the ability to establish diplomatic relations with other states. Williams claimed that Slozamastan fulfilled these conditions.</p>



<p>Williams&#8217; next plan is to get Slozamastan recognized as a micronation by the United States. However, it will not be easy for him to get this recognition.</p>



<p>Sultan said, &#8216;I have sent e-mails and private messages to US President Joe Biden on Facebook, Twitter, Instagram and MySpace but have not received any response. All my messages are unread. I was a bit disappointed by this. Perhaps the messages are stuck in his spam folder. But we will try.&#8217;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://2pp.over.tribler.org/travel-to-all-countries-is-over-this-time-he-made-his-own-country/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
